{
    "id": "a44924bddcfe4760a70708a676cb86bd",
    "title": "Infinitive Or Gerund Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I still miss ………………… in Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to live",
                "living",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef5c077130f34c51a088410f35731743"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy …………………. in the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "to swim"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2da9d5a98a54e2c91f6a38bb5b3371d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He avoided ………………….. his ex-girlfriend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meeting",
                "to meet"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cb8df13513b4c14a0316583c1520f98"
        },
        {
            "question": "You promised ………………… it by Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to finish",
                "finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2adc5dc86b354d7b95ec7f4f19ed4e67"
        },
        {
            "question": "She expected ………………… the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "481db32f306244768c158ac4bc148e21"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you like …………………. with me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "coming",
                "to come"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "11834705d9ff401f82c481fe8d99dc0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She taught me how ………………… it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eaa1d85231994c5da7790242c40aa357"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t feel like ………………… out tonight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3fada3edb5464343bc87fbc6c5fe84e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ………………….. the window?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to open",
                "opening"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b2e2df2aeb142f9aa230f398604cd97"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind my …………………. late?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "coming",
                "come",
                "to come"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b48dacf6b51e4d8ea9f0e85d02f7c5c4"
        }
    ]
}